BGM
So, here we go, the Candy Challenge!
Yes, that's right, this time it's a self-made interview.
Here's our guest this time, ladies and gentlemen!
This is Aira from AmeFlash!
Please give him my best regards! Hello, I'm Aira from AmeFlash. Nice to meet you!
ana
Your here to say
I would like to ask you a question right away.
I know you are all busy every day, but what do you do on your days off?
What do you do on your days off?
Recently, I've been trying to get out more.
And when I do go out, it's not for walking or shopping.
Well, I don't mean walking around shopping.
I mean, not... what's the word?
Not closet shopping.
It's lindo shopping!
Seriously, I didn't come out.
It's back.
Lind shopping.
Well, that's how I spend my time.
That's how I spend my time.
But when I'm at home, I'm basically sleeping or eating.
Or watching dramas and movies.
Can you tell us about one of your favorite movies?
It's a Korean drama.
It's a Korean drama called "Can't Stop Evil Spirits".
It's a drama about exterminating evil spirits.
It's not a horror drama, but it's about exterminating evil spirits.
It's not a horror drama.
It's not a horror drama, but it has some interesting elements.
Even if you don't like scary dramas
Even if you don't like scary things.
I've been watching it a lot lately.
I've been watching it for a while now.
I heard you have a new hobby.
What kind of hobby?
I'm really into going to bedrocks and saunas.I'm really into going to bedrock and going to saunas these days.
Sometimes I go to a bathhouse with a childhood friend.
One of the girls I grew up with told me she was into saunas.
I thought I was worse than that.
I felt embarrassed to use it alone.
So I decided to go with her.
I adjusted to the sauna and the water bath.
I adjusted to the sauna and the water bath, and then I went with her.
So I go to the sauna three times a week.
I used to have no idea how to really get in shape.
I couldn't even stay in the sauna for five minutes, so I would leave for about a minute right away.
I had to endure it for a little bit longer.
Then I tried to endure the water bath, and it felt really good.
I was hooked.
Next question: It's very hot right now, and it feels like summer, doesn't it?
Do you have any summer episodes?
Well, summer is all about ghosts, isn't it?
When I was on a road trip with my family, we happened to be driving.
We happened to be on a course around Porgy.
And when I looked at the time, it was around 12:30 at night.
We decided to take a course to go back home together.
When I was away from Porgy for a while, I looked at the time again, and it was 23:00.
I couldn't stop getting goosebumps, and I thought it was the scariest thing I had experienced in a long time.
That was a very scary experience.
I had goosebumps, but they got colder. It was cooler.
It was a bit scary. It was a summery story.
Next question.
Is there anything that has been important to you since you were a child?
There is one thing.
I'm curious about this.
There was a towelette that I had been using since I was zero years old.
It had a blue and white border, and the fibers felt so good.
I liked to play with the fibers between my fingernails because it felt so good.
But as the years went by, the towel got smaller and smaller, and at first it was only this small.
It got smaller and smaller when I went to bed, and I felt comfortable sleeping on it when I was nervous.
I didn't want her to lose it during PE, so I left it at home.
Then my mom threw away the towelette.
I was really angry when I came home and found out.When I got home, I found out, and I was really angry.
I couldn't believe it. I tried to find a replacement, and I managed to squelch both the governor and my anger.
Is there an ideal towelette?
I mean, a little firm fiber, coarse, fine stitches...
If you have any good coarse towelettes, please let me know.
Please let me know.
Next, I'd like to ask the last question.
Is it okay if I ask you a question that I normally wouldn't be able to ask you?
Can I ask you what type of man you like?
I think the best type is someone I can respect.
Someone who would move over for you as a matter of course.
Someone who can pick up things he dropped even if he didn't drop them.
Someone who can pay attention to details like that.
Is there anything you value second most?
You mean the second most important thing?
Someone who doesn't waste money?
Thank you very much for sharing with us something that we don't usually get to hear.
Thank you very much.
Our guest this time was Aira from Ame Arashi.